It smells good.
You should smell the lily, too.
Sniff, sniff.
All set. Are you girls ready?
Try to smile pretty for me.
Okay, say cheese.
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you.
So we had to cross the wall.
I had to have you all to myself.
Kirikuma!
Kirikuma Urochi!
Delicious smell, slurp.
Good morning, Kureha. Growl, growl.
Kinko, good morning. Growl, growl. Lick?
Kureha, you're close to me.
Wait a minute. What are you doing?
Seriously, why are you in my house again?
I moved in, growl.
Growl, growl! All done! We're finished moving in!
We're your roomies now.
Bottoms up!
New roomie noodles!
Come on, Kureha.
Bottoms up!
New roomie noodles!
Get out!
Get out of my house!
You have to leave.
And by the way, it's not acceptable to just move into someone's house without asking.
Growl, growl!
But Kureha, you ate your new roomie noodles!
So, I don't even get what that means.
Look, it's that one girl.
What? Oh, her. She's totally bad luck to her friends.
It's worse than bad luck. Students are disappearing. And the missing girls all happen to be from her class.
There, you heard them. Getting close to me is bad luck.
It's true. You're gonna get caught up in the invisible storm.
Do you really believe that?
Yes. If you two make friends with me, you'll just wind up excluded. Because that's the law of this herd. Understand now? Leave me alone for your own sake.
Growl, growl, growl! You're the one who doesn't understand, silly. Lulu told you, Ginkgo, and Lulu came here to make friends with you!
We'll protect Kureha from the invisible storm. And we promise we won't back down on love. Growl, growl.
I'm not lying. She was a bear masquerading as a human.
That's impossible.
I saw it. Mitsuko turned into a bear right in front of me. She ate Sumika. She killed my friend.
Mitsuko told me as much herself. And then... And then I...
I took my gun. And I aimed it right at her?
Kureha. That's enough of this story.
But it's true!
You poor darling. The shock was just too much, so you've clearly hallucinated.
No, it's real! I swear!
I won't force you to do anything right away. However, you will eventually need to accept the reality of the situation and let it go.
I just remembered. Next Sunday is your birthday. It is, isn't it?
Yes.
Rhea's little girl about to be 17. I can't believe it. Time certainly flies. So tell me, what would you like to do this year?
Go out for dinner? Or did you want a particular present?
No. Not this year.
Now that I think about it, you know your mother's pendant? She loved it so much. It was a present for her when she turned 17.
I'm actually the one who gave it to her.
Really? It was from you?
Yes. It was a symbol of a promise between friends. We pledged to each other that we would never forget love.
You pledged to never forget love?
We sure did. As long as you don't forget love, you'll never ever be truly alone.
And if you don't give up on love, even if you lose something, you'll never be invisible.
Of course, it's important to know that love can cause us pain as well. For example, when we remember time that's been lost.
Remember time that's been lost?
Sumika.
Whenever we feel that pain, we should try to focus on something else and not be too hard on ourselves.
Koreha, I think what you probably need right now more than anything is a new friend.
A new friend? Seriously?
Yes. Try allowing yourself to get close to someone else.
I can't do it.
What?
I don't want to get close to someone else. Sumika is my only friend. I'll never give up on love, no matter what.
Grow, growl, munch munch
Grow, growl, curry pie is eating one of those rolls again
But Lulu doesn't think they smell all that delicious
Krayha eats what tastes like love to her
What tastes like love?
Yes, it's something which can't be destroyed
By any storm or bear or human
Say what? Are you sure that's for real?
It's real, I'm sure
I don't know.
It's okay. I'm your friend. You don't have to be alone anymore. I'm here, and I love you. Lady Kumaria.
I remember getting love from someone. That's why I came. Why I crossed the wall.
Kureha, I want to have you. I want you all to myself.
Hey, Kureha. Got a sec, maybe?
I want you to know. We talked it over this morning. Everyone agreed we've been really cruel.
We know we're in the wrong, and we're beyond sorry for what we've done.
So, we want to make it up to you. Not just you. To Sumika, too.
Give me a break. You all excluded, Sumika. None of you have the right to be forgiven.
Why the change of heart now? If this is some sort of game, you girls better finish it.
Because I won't lose to people like you. You're not going to make me invisible.
Please, please forgive us. We've all been so... We've been so awful. We really are sorry.
What was that, Growl? Only we get to make friends with Kureha.
That girl is in our way. Big time.
Only one solution. Growl, Growl.
Hey, listen to this. Article 1. The way to a girl's heart is through her stomach.
Challenge accepted. Ginkgo and Lulu are going to make curry pie something she loves as much as those crazy rolls.
And then... Lulu is so clever.
Delicious smell. Growl, Growl.
No! You can't transform here. It doesn't matter how hungry you may be.
We have to follow court rules on this side. We're only allowed to eat the flesh of invisible girls, Ginkgo.
Growl.
So do you know what kinds of food Kureha likes?
Shiokara and spaghetti.
That sounds like what an old man would eat.
She's liked them since she was little.
Hmm. All right. Guess we know what tonight's dinner will be.
Growl, Growl! Welcome home, lady!
Um, what are you doing?
Making dinner. Growl, Growl.
Uh-huh. Ginkgo and Lulu have decided to make your love flavor.
Make what? My love flavor?
Yep! We're cooking your two favorite foods!
What? No way!
Yes! We call it Shiokara spaghetti!
Delicious smell, Growl, Growl.
Oh, wow! Incredible!
A flavor-pairing made in heaven!
Try one, Ginkgo! Cherry tomato!
Here comes Ginkgo! Try some creamy honey flan!
Eat this, Ginkgo! Creamy, lightly salted salmon!
Now it's your turn, Growl!
No thanks. I won't eat that.
What?
But why? We thought you were a fan of Shiokara and spaghetti, just like old men are!
Wait. How'd you know that?
We... did?
I'm certain I only ever told Sumika about that.
Two transfer students shouldn't know anything.
Hmm. Good point!
We don't know anything.
I'm serious. I want you to stay away from me!
Growl, but we want to be a sense, Curry pie!
Why is that so hard to understand?
Stop it!
Enough about being my friend. I'm sick of it.
Why is everyone trying to make me give up on my love?
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
I don't want new friends.
Sumika is my only love.
I don't want anyone else.
What's with you two?
Why are you so damn desperate to get close to me?
Growl, Growl!
That was super scary for Lulu.
Lulu thought for sure you were about to tell Curry pie the truth about everything.
But you know, Ginko, if you tell her, we can't be human girls anymore.
Those are the court's rules.
Sheesh!
Lulu hopes Curry pie remembers you soon.
This is getting exhausting.
Ginko, I'm here.
Your love!
Listen about earlier.
I'm sorry.
I was happy.
I just had a hard time admitting it.
Growl, Growl.
It's okay.
I understand.
I was thinking, if we took some time to wash each other all over,
it might give us the chance to really get to know one another.
Gorgeous snow.
What about that, Ginko?
Does it feel good?
Growl, yeah, it feels good.
And here, Ginko?
This spot?
Does it feel good?
Oh yeah, it does.
Really good.
And what about here?
How does this spot feel?
Really good.
Oh yeah, really good.
It's, it's amazing.
Here you go, Queen Esa-wistle!
Here, Kureha.
For you.
I know it's a little early.
What's that?
My birthday isn't for a while, you know.
Yeah, of course I do.
I can't explain it.
I just had to give you this today.
Okay, you are so silly.
Um, wait.
Don't open it yet.
What?
On your birthday, I want you to come to this spot.
Then you can read what it says.
Why then?
So that it's perfect, since it's my present to you.
You got me a gift?
How could I not?
Wait though to open it?
Please?
Yeah, sure thing.
Look at you.
Oh, such a beautiful smile.
I want you to always smile like that.
Like a flower.
That's my love.
It's funny.
Even if I had to watch you from a distance, I would be happy just to see that smile.
What are you talking about?
There's no distance between us.
I'm always right by your side.
That's true.
So, you kept your promise and didn't back down on love.
I'll never, ever forget that either.
Sumika?
They'll bloom soon, won't they?
Yeah.
Oh, Sumika.
You're my only friend.
And the only friend I want.
The flower bed.
We asked the school to help you grow flowers again.
I'm sorry about what happened yesterday.
We all are really sorry, Koriha.
The invisible storm wrecked this place, but we want to fix it now.
We'll do whatever it takes.
Our thought was to refill it with flowers.
We were hoping we could work together to make Sumika's last wish come true.
Last wish?
What do you know about it?
Well, we know it has to do with your birthday, which is next week, right?
Yeah, that's right.
You see, I heard that before, uh, before what happened to Sumika happened, that she said, um...
What?
She said she wanted a party.
One for you.
And she wanted it in a garden full of flowers.
So that it's perfect, since it's my present to you.
Sumika.
Well, we're asking you to allow us to celebrate your birthday this year.
Because that...
That's what Sumika wanted.
Please, for Sumika's sake.
Oh, what's with that?
Bingo and Lulu are her friends, not those stinking girls.
You agree, yeah?
Yeah.
We don't have much time before Kureha's birthday.
Let's start today, okay, girls?
Okay!
Ladies, thank you for working so hard these past few days.
Because of everyone here, Kureha Tsubaki has started to believe that we are interested in being her friends.
We only need to endure her a little longer.
At this moment, we will confirm our feelings and make a final decision.
Who is the evil we must exclude?
Let's search evil!
Select.
We have chosen Kureha Tsubaki as the evil to exclude.
Growl, growl.
This is great news.
Turns out she is an invisible girl, meaning we can eat her after all.
Guess he'll be judged this time, growl, growl.
Let the Yuri trial begin.
I wish to eat her.
That way I can save Kureha from the invisible storm, growl, growl.
Not this again.
Excuse me, but doesn't everyone want to protect the girl they love?
Sparkle, sparkle.
Meh.
I wouldn't be too certain.
Huh?
Defendant bears.
So far you've eaten several humans affiliated with this invisible storm.
All in the name of saving Kureha Tsubaki.
Is that correct?
Yes.
They're guilty, your honor.
Ginko Yurishiro, answer this question honestly, please.
What is it that you want?
And don't say to save Kureha.
That's just an excuse.
In fact, isn't it true all you really want is to make sure you are Kureha Tsubaki's one and only friend?
Objection!
Speculation!
The prosecutor is being ruled by his personal sadism!
For your information, Ginko just wants to give back the love she got from Kurepai.
She wants a promised kiss.
Is that so wrong?
Order!
The objection is overruled.
Ginko Yurishiro, please answer the prosecutor's question.
Okay.
The truth is, I want to have Kureha onto myself.
Ginko?
I want to be friends with her again, and I want to have Kureha's love again.
That's the only reason I came here.
That's the reason I crossed the wall and dragged Lulu into it with me.
But Ginko, Lulu wanted to cross the wall with you.
It doesn't matter though, I won't back down on love.
I'll still do whatever it takes for love.
I'll do anything.
There's no going back now.
I've committed a serious crime.
Uh, Ginko?
What serious crime do you mean?
I mean...
Whoa!
No need to finish that sentence, okay?
This is too much.
Your honor.
The defendant bear confessed in court.
She just admitted to committing a crime.
You must find her guilty at once.
Ginko Yurishiro, is your love the real thing?
You bet it is.
And what if it's an egotistical love?
What if that pride eventually destroys you?
That's fine, because I'm a criminal bear.
I see.
Defendant bears, I ask you.
Do you want to be invisible, or would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat.
Bring on the humans!
Growl! Growl!
I am now ready to declare the verdicts.
Yuri, approved!
What did you want to meet me for?
It's kind of late.
Growl!
This is about Kareha.
Ginko and Lulu are going to be friends with her.
Huh?
What is that supposed to mean?
It means we won't let you have your way.
We're on to you, so now you disappear!
Shuck!
Kuma Shuck!
No!
This can't be real.
Are you two what I think?
No.
You just can't be.
Growl.
But we are.
We're bears and we'll eat you up, Growl.
Help!
Someone help me!
Ah!
One bear successfully eliminated by our trap.
We know what you two really are, and this is what you get.
Kareha...